[


	{
		"id": "java-1",
		"question": "What does this code segment print? <div class=\"code\">static void increment(int index) { <br> &ensp;index++; <br>} <br> <br>public static void main(String[] args){ <br>  &ensp;int i = 0; <br>  &ensp;increment(i); <br> &ensp;i++; <br>  &ensp;System.out.println(i); <br>}</div>",
		"correct_answer": "1",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"3",
			"0",
			"2"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "java-2",
		"question": "What class can use a method from another class without a visibility modifier?",
		"correct_answer": "Any class from the same package",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Any class",
			"Any class that extends this class",
			"Any class from any subpackage of this package"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "java-3",
		"question": "What is an unchecked exception?",
		"correct_answer": "An exception that extends RuntimeException of Error that you do not need to catch or rethrow",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"An exception that extends RuntimeException that you may catch but cannot rethrow",
			"An exception that can be of any type, and that you do not need to catch or rethrow",
			"An exception that extends RuntimeException that you cannot catch but can rethrow"
		],
		"fr": "https://blog.octo.com/la-gestion-des-exceptions-en-java/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-4",
		"question": "How can you add a method to an existing interface without having to modify the classes that already implement it?",
		"correct_answer": "You make this method a default method",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"You provide an implementation of this method in a separate static class",
			"You make this method an abstract class",
			"You cannot add a method to an interface without implementing in the existing implementing classes"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "java-5",
		"question": "What does a class need to do when it declares that it is implementing an interface?",
		"correct_answer": "It must be declared as abstract OR implement each of the interface's abstract methods, apart from the methods of the Object class.",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"It must implement each of the interface's abstract methods and override the default methods",
			"It must be declared as abstract",
			"It must implement each of the interface's abstract methods"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "java-6",
		"question": "What will be the output of the following program? <div class=\"code\"><p>public class MyFirst {</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;public static void main(String[] args) {</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; MyFirst obj =newMyFirst(n);</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;}</p><p><br></p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;static int a = 10;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;static int n;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;int b = 5;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;int c;</p><p><br></p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;public MyFirst(int m) {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp; System.out.println(a + &quot;, &quot; + b + &quot;, &quot; + c + &quot;, &quot; + n + &quot;, &quot;+m);</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;}</p><p><br></p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;// Instance Block</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;{</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; b= 30;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; n = 20;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;}</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;// Static Block</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;static {</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; a = 60;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;}</p><p>}</p></div>",
		"correct_answer": " 60, 30, 0, 20, 0",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"10, 5, 0, 20, 0",
			"10, 30, 20",
			"60, 5, 0, 20"
		],
		"source": "https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-7",
		"question": "Which of the following option leads to the portability and security of Java?",
		"correct_answer": "Bytecode is executed by JVM",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"The applet makes the Java code secure and portable",
			"Use of exception handling",
			"Dynamic binding between objects"
		],
		"source": "https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-8",
		"question": "What is the return type of the hashCode() method in the Object class?",
		"correct_answer": "int",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Object",
			"long",
			"void"
		],
		"source": "https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-9",
		"question": "What does the expression float a = 35 / 0 return?",
		"correct_answer": "Infinity",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"0",
			"Not a Number",
			"Run time exception"
		],
		"source": "https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-10",
		"question": " Evaluate the following Java expression, if x=3, y=5, and z=10: <div class=\"code\">++z + y - y + z + x++ </div>",
		"correct_answer": "25",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"20",
			"23",
			"24"
		],
		"source": "https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-11",
		"question": "What will be the output of the following program? <div class=\"code\"><p>public class Test { &nbsp;</p><p>public static void main(String[] args) { &nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; int count = 1; &nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; while (count &lt;= 15) { &nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; System.out.println(count % 2 == 1 ?&quot;***&quot;: &quot;+++++&quot;); &nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; ++count; &nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; }</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; }</p><p>&nbsp;} &nbsp;</p></div>",
		"correct_answer": "8 times *** and 7 times +++++",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"15 times ***",
			"15 times +++++",
			"Both will print only once"
		],
		"source": "https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-12",
		"question": "Which of the following for loop declaration is not valid?",
		"correct_answer": "<div class=\"codeAnswer\">for ( int i = 99; i >= 0; i / 9 )</div>",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">for ( int i = 7; i <= 77; i += 7 )</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">for ( int i = 20; i >= 2; - -i )</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">for ( int i = 2; i <= 20; i = 2* i )</div>"
		],
		"source": "https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-13",
		"question": "Which of the following is true about the anonymous inner class?",
		"correct_answer": "It has no class name",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"It has only methods",
			"Objects can't be created",
			"It has a fixed class name"
		],
		"source": "https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-14",
		"question": "Which option is false about the final keyword?",
		"correct_answer": "A final class cannot extend other classes.",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"A final method cannot be overridden in its subclasses.",
			"A final class cannot be extended.",
			"A final method can be inherited."
		],
		"source": "https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-15",
		"question": "Given that Student is a class, how many reference variables and objects are created by the following code? <div class=\"code\"><p>Student studentName, studentId;</p><p>studentName = new Student();</p><p>Student stud_class = new Student();</p></div>",
		"correct_answer": "Three reference variables and two objects are created.",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Two reference variables and two objects are created.",
			"One reference variable and two objects are created.",
			"Three reference variables and three objects are created."
		],
		"source": "https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-16",
		"question": "Which of the following is a valid syntax to synchronize the HashMap?",
		"correct_answer": "<div class=\"codeAnswer\">Map m1 = Collections.synchronizedMap(hashMap); </div>",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\"> Map m = hashMap.synchronizeMap();</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\"> HashMap map =hashMap.synchronizeMap();</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\"> Map m2 = Collection.synchronizeMap(hashMap);</div>"
		],
		"source": "https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-17",
		"question": "<p>Given that strings is an ArrayList with the following elements: &quot;one&quot;, &quot;two&quot; and &quot;three&quot;, what does the following code do?</p><div class=\"code\"><p>for (string s : strings){</p><p><span>&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;</span>System.out.println(&quot;s = &quot; + s);</p><p><span>&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;</span>strings.remove(&quot;two&quot;);</p><p>}</p></div>",
		"correct_answer": "The code throws a ConcurrentModificationException",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"The code throws a ArrayOutModificationException",
			"The code prints \"one\" and then \"three\"",
			"The code throws an IllegalStateException"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-18",
		"question": "<p>You have the following code</p><div class=\"code\"><p>try (Reader reader1 = new FileReader(&quot;log.txt&quot;);</p><p>&nbsp; Reader reader2 = new FileReader(&quot;log.txt&quot;)){</p><p>&nbsp; // some code</p><p>} catch (IOException e){</p><p>}</p></div><p>At run time, the constructor of reader2 throws an IOException, and the close() method of reader1 also throws an IOException. What exception(s) is/are caught in this code ?</p>",
		"correct_answer": "The exception thrown by the construction of reader2",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"The exception thrown by the closing of reader1",
			"A third exception is caught, wrapping the two first exceptions",
			"Both exceptions are caught"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-19",
		"question": "You need to concatenate a list of instances of String together. What precautions should you take ?",
		"correct_answer": "Avoid the unnecessary creation of instances of String",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Properly flush the buffer of string in the returned String",
			"Properly flush the buffer of strings",
			"Make sure all the elements of the list are properly consumed"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-20",
		"question": "You need to distribute your application as a JAR file on the internet. How can you make your customer sure that the JAR they will download has not been modified by anyone?",
		"correct_answer": "You can sign it so that the JVM can check for its integrity",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"You can distribute a password along with it",
			"You can distribute a hash code along with it",
			"You can hash each class in it"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-21",
		"question": "What will be the output of the following program? <div class=\"code\"><p>public class MyFirst {</p><p><span>&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;</span>public static void main(String[] args) {</p><p><span>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;</span>System.out.println(&quot;main&quot;);</p><p><span>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;</span>MyFirst obj = new MyFirst(n);</p><p><span>&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;</span>}</p><p><span>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span>public MyFirst(int m) {</p><p><span>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;</span>System.out.println(&quot;constructor&quot;);</p><p><span>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span>}</p><p><span>&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;</span>{</p><p><span>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span>System.out.println(&quot;instance&quot;);</p><p><span>&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;</span>}</p><p><span>&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;</span>static {</p><p><span>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span>System.out.println(&quot;static&quot;);</p><p><span>&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;</span>}</p><p>}</p></div>",
		"correct_answer": "static -> main -> instance -> constructor",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"main -> constructor -> static -> instance",
			"main -> static -> constructor -> instance",
			"static -> instance -> main -> constructor"
		],
		"source": "self"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-22",
		"question": "<p>The following code is a part of a Java program&nbsp;</p><div class=\"code\"><p>String a = &quot;Hello&quot;;</p><p>String b = &quot; World&quot;;</p><p>a.concat(b);</p></div><p>How many instances of <span class=\"codeInLine\">String</span> are created at the end of the program?</p>",
		"correct_answer": "3",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"2",
			"4",
			"1"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-23",
		"question": "You need to call a method that throws <span class=\"codeInLine\">IOException</span> and <span class=\"codeInLine\">FileNotFoundException</span>. Knowing that <span class=\"codeInLine\">FileNotFoundException</span> is an extension of <span class=\"codeInLine\">IOException</span>, among the following catch clauses, which one is NOT correct?",
		"correct_answer": "<div class=\"codeAnswer\">catch(FileNotFoundException e){}catch(IOException e){}</div>",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">catch(FileNotFoundException | IOException e){}</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">catch(Exception e){}</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">catch(IOException e){}</div>"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-24",
		"question": "The maximum value you can store in an int is 2147483647. What does the following code print out? <div class=\"code\"><p>public static void main(String[] args){</p><p>&nbsp; int max = 2147483647;</p><p>&nbsp;System.out.println(max+1);</p><p>}</p></div>",
		"correct_answer": "-2147483648",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"-1",
			"It throws an OperationOverflowException",
			"0"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-25",
		"question": "Which functional interface does not return a value?",
		"correct_answer": "Consumer",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Unary operator",
			"Supplier",
			"Predicate"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-26",
		"question": "Why are Java streams considered lazy?",
		"correct_answer": "Because intermediate operations are not evaluated until the terminal operation is invoked",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Because, when the terminal operation is called, traversal of streams begins and the associated function is performed one by one",
			"Because intermediate operations are evaluated before the terminal operation is invoked",
			"Because, when the intermediate operation is called, traversal of streams begins and the associated function is performed one by one"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-27",
		"question": "You have a stream of strings of characters. You want to concatenate all those strings using a comma as a separator. How do you proceed?",
		"correct_answer": "Collect the elements using the Collectors.joining() collector, passing the comma as a parameter.",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Collect the elements in a StringJoiner and call join() on that object, passing the comma as a parameter.",
			"Reduce the stream in a StringBuilder, using the StringBuilder::add as the reduction function.",
			"Collect the elements in a list and call join() on that list, passing the comma as a parameter."
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-28",
		"question": "What does it mean for a field to be final?",
		"correct_answer": "Its value must be set during the construction of the object and cannot be modified.",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"The field cannot be overridden in any extension this class may have.",
			"Once set, its value can only be modified within the instance initializer block.",
			"The field is a constant, accessible from all the class instances."
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-29",
		"question": "<p>Given the following code:&nbsp;</p><div class=\"code\"><p>public static void main(String[] args) {</p><p>&nbsp; int myInt = 2;</p><p>&nbsp; float myFloat = 3.8f;</p><p>&nbsp; double myDouble = 2.9;</p><p>&nbsp; char myChar = &apos;P&apos;;</p><p>}</p></div><p>Which is a valid assignment operation?</p><p><br></p>",
		"correct_answer": "<div class=\"codeAnswer\">myInt = myChar;</div>",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">myChar = myInt;</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">myInt = myFloat;</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">myFloat = myDouble;</div>"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-30",
		"question": "<p>What will happen when you write the following code?&nbsp;</p><div class=\"code\"><p>class Animal {</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; //variables, constructors and methods</p><p>}</p><p>public class MainClass {</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; public static void main(String[] args) {</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Animal animal;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; System.out.println(animal);</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; }</p><p>}</p></div>",
		"correct_answer": "A syntax error stating that the animal variable must be instantiated",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"&quot;null&quot; will be printed to the console.",
			"&quot;animal&quot; will be printed to the console.",
			"A NullPointerException when you run the application"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-31",
		"question": "You have a class Person with an age property of type int and its corresponding getter getAge(). You have a stream of instances of this class and want to divide this stream into two lists: the first containing the people younger than or equal to 20, and the other the people older than 20. Which collector can you use?",
		"correct_answer": "<div class=\"codeAnswer\">Collectors.partitioningBy(p -> p.getAge() > 20, toList())</div>",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">Collectors.partitioningBy(age -> age > 20, toList())</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">Collectors.groupingBy(Person::getAge, comparing(p -> p.getAge() > 20))</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">Collectors.groupingBy(Person::getAge, comparing(age -> age > 20))</div>"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-32",
		"question": "You must create a size() method in an interface and provide an implementation. How do you declare this method?",
		"correct_answer": "<div class=\"codeAnswer\">default int size() { /* method implementation */ }</div>",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">concrete int size() { /* method implementation */ }</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">final int size() { /* method implementation */ }</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">int size() { /* method implementation */ }</div>"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-33",
		"question": "What do you need to make an interface a functional interface?",
		"correct_answer": "Make sure it has only one abstract method that needs to be implemented.",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Remove its static methods.",
			"Remove its default methods.",
			"Annotate it with @FunctionalInterface. "
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-34",
		"question": "You have a User class with a single field: name. In your application, two instances of User are the same if they have the same name. Keeping in mind the optimized program performance and efficient object comparison, how can you enforce such a rule?",
		"correct_answer": "By overriding the equals(Object) and hashCode() methods in the User class",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"By creating an equals(User) and overriding the hashCode() method in the User class",
			"By only creating an equals(User) method in the User class",
			"By only overriding an equals(Object) method in the User class"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-35",
		"question": "How can a final field be set to a value?",
		"correct_answer": "By using an initializer or by setting it in a constructor",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"By using an initializer only",
			"By setting it in a constructor only",
			"By using an initializer and by optionally modifying this value in a constructor"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-36",
		"question": "What is true of a Stream?",
		"correct_answer": "Streams don't store their elements.",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Streams support indexed access to their elements.",
			"Streams are reusable.",
			"Streams are mutable."
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-37",
		"question": "You have a <span class=\"code\">Map&lt;Integer, String&gt;</span>. This Map does not allow null values. You call the <span class=\"code\">get()</span> method with a key that is not present in it. What does this method return?",
		"correct_answer": "null",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"An empty String",
			"NoSuchElementException",
			"NullPointerException"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-38",
		"question": "You want to package an application composed of many class files in a single Java Archive (JAR) and make it executable. How will you proceed?",
		"correct_answer": "Create a single JAR file containing a MANIFEST.mf file with a reference to the class that contains the main() method.",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Create a single JAR file containing a MANIFEST.mf file with a reference to all the classes of that JAR.",
			"Create one JAR file per module, put a MANIFEST.mf with a reference to the class that contains the main() method in one of them, and launch that JAR.",
			"Package each module in a JAR, then package them in a meta-JAR, put a reference to the class that contains the main() method in this meta-JAR, and launch that JAR."
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-39",
		"question": "You wrote a method that takes an index (of type int) in a list as a parameter. Which properly documents this parameter in the Javadoc?",
		"correct_answer": "@param index the index in the list",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"@param int index the index in the list",
			"@parameter int index the index in the list",
			"@parameter index the index in the list"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-40",
		"question": "You want to add the content of an optional to a list. How do you proceed?",
		"correct_answer": "Call the following on the optional object: <span class=\"codeAnswer\">ifPresent(list::add)</span>",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Call the following on the optional object: <span class=\"codeAnswer\">orElse(list::add)</span>",
			"Call the following on the optional object: <span class=\"codeAnswer\">list.Add(<item>)</span>",
			"Call the following on the optional object: <span class=\"codeAnswer\">isPresent(list::add)</span>"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-41",
		"question": "You must create a collection of strings. You want to guarantee that the iteration over this collection will be in the lexicographic order of the strings. What class will you use?",
		"correct_answer": "A TreeSet",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"A HashSet",
			"An ArrayList",
			"A LinkedList"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-42",
		"question": "You must sort a stream of strings of characters from the shortest string to the longest. How do you proceed?",
		"correct_answer": "Sort the stream by passing the comparator of strings that compares the length of the strings.",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Collect the stream in a SortedSet built with the right comparator.",
			"Map the strings to their length, then sort the result.",
			"Collect the stream in a TreeMap where the keys are the length of the strings, then extract the ordered values."
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-43",
		"question": "Given the following abstract class: <div class=\"code\"><p>public abstract class AbstractTesting {</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; public abstract int size();</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; public boolean isEmpty() {</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; return size() == 0;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; }</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; public AbstractTesting() {&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; }</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; abstract int getSize() {</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; return size;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; }</p><p>}</p></div> Which part of this class will result in a syntax error?",
		"correct_answer": "The <span class=\"codeAnswer\">getSize()</span> method ",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"The <span class=\"codeAnswer\">isEmpty()</span> method",
			"The <span class=\"codeAnswer\">AbstractTesting()</span> constructor",
			"The <span class=\"codeAnswer\">size</span> variable "
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-44",
		"question": "You have the following code:<div class=\"code\"><p>WorkOrder wo = new WorkOrder() {</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; modelNumber = &quot;LIF-42&quot;</p><p>};</p></div>For this code to successfully compile, what must WorkOrder contain?",
		"correct_answer": "A default constructor and an editable String property modelNumber",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"A constructor that takes a String parameter, and a String attribute which will set a modelNumber",
			"A String attribute which will set a modelNumber",
			"A constructor that takes a String parameter, which sets a modelNumber"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-45",
		"question": "How does a TreeMap store its key-value pairs?",
		"correct_answer": "It uses a red black tree",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"It puts the keys in an array with pointers to the values",
			"It uses a skip list of key value pairs",
			"It uses a set of Map.Entry objects"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-46",
		"question": "You need a class to handle sequences of characters. In your application, you must put these sequences in upper case and lower case and compare them between themselves. What class can you use?",
		"correct_answer": "The String class",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"The StringBuffer class",
			"The StringBuilder class",
			"The StringJoiner class"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-47",
		"question": "What does this code print out?<p></p><p></p><p><div class=\"code\"></p><p>int[] tab = {1, 2, 3, 4};</p><p></p><p>int loop = 0;</p><p>for (int i : tab) {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;loop++;</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;if (i > 2)</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;break;</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;loop++;</p><p>}</p><p>System.out.println(\"loop = \" + loop);</p></div>",
		"correct_answer": "loop = 5",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"loop = 6",
			"loop = 2",
			"loop = 4"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-48",
		"question": "<p>You have the following functional interface: </p><p></p><p><div class=\"code\"></p><p>@FunctionalInterface</p><p>interface DoSomeMath {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;int calculate(int x);</p><p>}</p></div> What change to this interface will cause an error?",
		"correct_answer": "<p>Adding the following:</p> <div class=\"codeAnswer\">int subtract(int a, int b);</div>",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"<p>Adding the following:</p>  <div class=\"codeAnswer\">public static final int myInt = 0;</div>",
			"<p>Adding the following:</p>  <div class=\"codeAnswer\">public int myInt = 0;</div>",
			"Removing the <span class=\"codeAnswer\">@FunctionalInterface</span> annotation"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-49",
		"question": "<p>Why doesn't the following code compile?</p><p></p><p><div class=\"code\"></p><p>int i1 = 40_000;</p><p>short i2 = i1 + 10;</p></div>",
		"correct_answer": "Because the addition returns an int, which cannot be converted to a short without an explicit cast",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Because the addition returns a long, which cannot be cast to a short",
			"Because 40_000 is not a valid number in Java",
			"Because it is not possible to have a short greater than 32,767"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-50",
		"question": "<p>You have the two following classes:</p><p></p><p><div class=\"code\"></p><p>public class Queue {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;public static final int MAX_SIZE = 10;</p><p>}</p></div><div class=\"code\"><p>public class Consumer {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;static final int MAX_QUEUE_SIZE = Queue.MAX_SIZE;</p><p>}</p><p></div></p><p></p><p>These two classes happen to be in two different modules of your application. On day one, you compile both modules and deploy them in production. On day two, you modify the Queue class, by setting the MAX_SIZE value to 20. You compile the Queue module and deploy it in production. What happens when you launch your application?</p>",
		"correct_answer": "The value of Consumer.MAX_QUEUE_SIZE is still 10.",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"The value of Consumer.MAX_QUEUE_SIZE is set to 20.",
			"A RuntimeException is raised when you try to read the MAX_QUEUE_SIZE value.",
			"A RuntimeException is raised when the application is launched."
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-51",
		"question": "<p>You are using the reduce() method to calculate the combined age of people in a group. You have the following code which tries to do that: </p><p></p><p><div class=\"code\"></p><p>//assume implementation of a Person class that has a constructor for name </p><p>//and age, along with appropriate set and get methods</p><p>List<Person> people = Arrays.asList(new Person(\"Person 1\", 20), new Person(\"Person 2\", 25));</p><p>int result = people.stream().reduce(0, (currAge, user) -> currAge + user.getAge());</p><p>System.out.println(result);</p></div><p>This results in a syntax error. How can you change this to make it print out 45?</p>",
		"correct_answer": "Use a combiner <div class=\"codeAnswer\">int result = people.stream().reduce(0, (currAge, user) -> currAge +  user.getAge(), Integer::sum);</div>",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Change the type of \"result\" from an int to a double <div class=\"codeAnswer\">double result = people.stream().reduce(0, (currAge, user) -> currAge + user.getAge());</div>",
			"Change the type of \"result\" from an int to a float <div class=\"codeAnswer\">float result = people.stream().reduce(0, (currAge, user) -> currAge + user.getAge());</div>",
			"Remove the first argument in the reduce() method <div class=\"codeAnswer\">int result = people.stream().reduce((currAge, user) -> currAge + user.getAge());</div>"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-52",
		"question": "What action would work when writing a method reference?",
		"correct_answer": "Calling of an instance method through the name of a class; for example: containingObject::instanceMethodName",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Passing a final parameter ",
			"Passing a non-final parameter",
			"Calling a static method through an instance variable; for example: <div class=\"codeAnswer\">instancevariable::staticMethodName</div>"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-53",
		"question": "Which of Java's five functional interfaces operates on two reference types?",
		"correct_answer": "BinaryOperator",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"DoublePredicate",
			"Consumer",
			"Supplier"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-54",
		"question": "Which type of variable is created in a class, but located outside of all methods and constructors, and is visible to all methods and constructors of that class?",
		"correct_answer": "An instance variable ",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"A parameter",
			"A local variable ",
			"A global variable"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-55",
		"question": "<p>You have two classes:</p><p></p><p><div class=\"code\"></p><p>public class Holder {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;public String toString() {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;return \"I am a holder\";</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;}</p><p>}</p><p></div></p><p></p><p><div class=\"code\"></p><p>public class ExtendedHolder extends Holder {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;public String toString() {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   return \"I am an extended holder\";</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;}</p><p>}</p><p></div></p><p></p><p>What does the following code print out when executed?</p><p><div class=\"code\"></p><p>public class Main {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;public static void display(Holder holder) {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Object o = holder;</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;System.out.println(o.toString());</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;}</p><p></p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;public static void main(String[] args) {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Holder holder = new ExtendedHolder();</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;display(holder);</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;}</p><p>}</p><p></div></p><p></p>",
		"correct_answer": "I am an extended holder",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"<p>I am an extended holder</p><p>I am a holder</p><p>java.lang.Object@4e04a765 (the number may vary)</p>",
			"I am a holder",
			"java.lang.Object@4e04a765 (the number may vary)"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-56",
		"question": "How can you create a stream from the elements of a List variable called list?",
		"correct_answer": "By calling list.stream()",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"By calling Arrays.stream(list.toArray())",
			"By calling Stream.of(list)",
			"By calling List.streamOf(list)"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-57",
		"question": "<p>You create a string of characters and then you trim it. Next, you put it in upper case and finally extract the first three characters using the substring method.</p><p></p><p>How many instances of the string would be created after the entire process of string operations?</p>",
		"correct_answer": "4",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"2",
			"3",
			"1"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-58",
		"question": "You must create a new stream of names, but you do not yet have any elements to put in. How can you do this?",
		"correct_answer": "<div class=\"codeAnswer\">Stream<String> names = Stream.empty();</div>",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">Stream<String> names = Stream.create();</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">Stream.empty();</div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\">Stream<String> names = Stream.new();</div>"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-59",
		"question": "What command must you use to execute a Main class that contains a main() method?",
		"correct_answer": "java Main",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Main",
			"java Main.class",
			"java Main.main()"
		],
		"source": ""
	},

	{
		"id": "java-60",
		"question": "What is a lambda expression in Java?",
		"correct_answer": "An implementation of any functional interface",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"An implementation of any interface",
			"An implementation of an interface that must be defined in the java.util.function package",
			"An implementation of any function"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-61",
		"question": "Using which type within a switch statement's test expression would result in a syntax error?",
		"correct_answer": "boolean",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"int",
			"enum",
			"String"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-62",
		"question": "<p>What does the following code print out?</p><p></p><div class=\"code\"><p>int i = 2;</p><p>int result = -1;</p><p>switch(i) {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;case 1: result = 1;</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;break;</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;case 2: result = 2;</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;case 3: result = 3;</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;case 4: result = 4;</p><p>}</p><p>System.out.println(\"result = \" + result);</div></p><p></p><p></p>",
		"correct_answer": "result = 4",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"result = 2",
			"result = 1",
			"result = -1"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-63",
		"question": "<p>Consider the following code: </p><div class=\"code\"><p>ArrayList<String> arrayListObject = new ArrayList<>(); </p><p>arrayListObject.add(\"B\");</p><p>arrayListObject.add(\"D\");</p><p>arrayListObject.add(\"A\");</p><p>arrayListObject.add(\"C\");</p></div><p>How can you sort the list of these letters in alphabetical order?</p>",
		"correct_answer": "<div class=\"codeAnswer\"><p>arrayListObject = (ArrayList<String>) arrayListObject</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;.stream()</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;.sorted()</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;.collect(Collectors.toList());</p></div>",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\"><p>arrayListObject = (ArrayList<String>) arrayListObject</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;.collect(Collectors.toList());</p></div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\"><p>arrayListObject.stream()</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;.sort();</p></div>",
			"<div class=\"codeAnswer\"><p>arrayListObject = (ArrayList<String>) arrayListObject.stream()</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;.sort();</p></div>"
		],
		"source": ""
	},

	{
		"id": "java-64",
		"question": "<p>You have the following class:</p><p><div class=\"code\"><p>public class Holder {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp;static String MAX_SIZE = System.getProperty(\"max.size\");</p><p>}</p></div></p><p>You execute the following code:</p><p><div class=\"code\"><p>Holder holder1 = new Holder();</p><p>Holder holder2 = new Holder();</p></div></p><p>How many times is the getProperty(\"max.size\") method called?</p>",
		"correct_answer": "1",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"2",
			"0 because this code will get an exception ",
			"0 because this property never gets initialized"
		],
		"source": ""
	},
	{
		"id": "java-65",
		"question": "How can you declare that a class ArrayList can use the methods of the AbstractList class, is of type Serializable, and provides implementations for the methods of List?",
		"correct_answer": "class ArrayList extends AbstractList implements List, Serializable",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"class ArrayList implements List, Serializable extends AbstractList",
			"class ArrayList::AbstractList implements List, Serializable",
			"class ArrayList extends AbstractList implements List as Serializable"
		],
		"source": ""
	}

]